mp3videosearch.com 2012-06-09

# MP3VideoSearch.com | Privacy Policy | Fastest MP3 Downloader

This Privacy Policy covers this web site’s treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you agree to receive e-mail marketing from us. It is important that visitors are fully informed about the use of their personal information. We believe in 100% permission-based marketing. Your privacy is very important to us. Upon subscription, your email address is protected and will not be shared, sold or rented to any third parties.

You may unsubscribe from any of our e-mail marketing programs at any time. In every e-mail communication we send, there is an unsubscribe hyperlink that allows the recipient to unsubscribe from the specific marketing program by simply clicking the hyperlink provided and following the instructions that follow. We attempt to process all unsubscribe requests in a prompt fashion. 

Our company reserves the right to provide aggregate or group data about our Users for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage, or characteristics of participants as a group, without disclosing personally identifiable information.

Additionally, when you open, preview or click on the advertising portion of our e-mails and/or those of our marketing partners and/or our affiliates, you have agreed to the terms set forth in our Privacy Policy and agree that as a function of opening, previewing or clicking on the advertising portion of our e-mails, that you will receive new or additional marketing communications from us, our marketing partners and/or our affiliates.

We also reserve the right to release current or past User information in the event that our company believes that the User is using, or has used, our services in violation of the terms and conditions, to commit unlawful acts, if the information is subpoenaed, if our company is sold or acquired, or when we deem it necessary or appropriate. By agreeing to these terms, you hereby consent to the disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when our company, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate.

We endeavor to safeguard and protect our Users information. When Users submit information at the website, their information is protected both online and off-line. The privacy of Users personal information is very important to us. Our employees are committed to our privacy and security policies.

No information should be submitted to, or posted at, any website by visitors under 18 years of age without the prior consent of their parent or guardian. Notwithstanding the foregoing, children 18 years of age and younger are not permitted to access this website and we do not knowingly collect personal information from such children. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

Users may receive e-mail confirming their registration with this site as well as promotional marketing of commercial products and services.

Our company does not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of each of the advertisers and/or third parties accessible through this website.

This Privacy Policy applies to consumers that have signed up on our website. We may use the personal information that you supply to us to bring selected retail opportunities to our members via direct mail, email and telemarketing. We may use businesses that provide any but not limited to the following services; direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation and email marketing.

Your Acceptance of These Terms By using this site, including, without limitation, signing up for offers and/or continuing to receive information from us, you agree to our Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on this website. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this website or acceptance of our emails following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept these changes and agree to continue receiving emails from us. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not register on this site.

_Revised 02-28-2006_
